<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on </title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//localhost:1313/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/home/about/</guid>
      <description>FMTea 2019 Formal Methods Teaching Workshop and Tutorial Event affiliated with FM 2019, 3rd World Congress on Formal Methods 
--Invited speaker Carroll Morgan, University of New South Wales, Australia
Registration Registration is now open.
Program Schedule of talks is available here.
Proceedings The proceedings is available here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/home/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/home/skills/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Objectives and Scope</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/home/objectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/home/objectives/</guid>
      <description>Formal Methods provide software engineering with tools and techniques for rigorously reasoning about the correctness of systems. While in recent years formal methods are increasingly being used in industry, university curricula are not adapting at the same pace. Some existing formal methods classes interest and challenge students, whereas others fail to ignite student motivation. We need to find ways to teach formal methods to the next generation, and doing so will require us to adapt our teaching to the 21st century students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organisation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/home/organisation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/home/organisation/</guid>
      <description>FMTea19 is organised by FME’s Teaching Committee. Our broad aim is to support a worldwide improvement in learning Formal Methods, mainly by teaching but also via self-learning. To that end, we started to collect a list of FM courses taught worldwide (https://github.com/luigiapetre/Formal-Methods-Courses/issues) and plan to collect other resources as well, such as FM case studies, FM inspirational papers, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program Committee</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/home/committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/home/committee/</guid>
      <description> Luigia Petre, Åbo Akademi University, Finland (co-chair) Brijesh Dongol, University of Surrey, UK (co-chair) Graeme Smith, University of Queensland, Australia (co-chair) Catherine Dubois, ENSIIE, France Joao F. Ferreira, University of Lisbon, Portugal K. Rustan M. Leino, Amazon Web Services, US Alexandra Mendes, University of Beira Interior, Portugal Leila Ribeiro, Federal University of Rio Grande do Sul, Brazil Pierluigi San Pietro, Politecnico di Milano, Italy Kenji Taguchi, CAV, Japan  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Previous Editions</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/home/previous/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/home/previous/</guid>
      <description>Several events focused on teaching aspects for Formal Methods were held in the beginning of the 2000s: two BCS-FACS TFM workshops (Oxford in 2003 and London in 2006), the TFM 2004 conference in Ghent (with proceedings published as Springer LNCS Volume 3294), the FM-Ed 2006 workshop (Hamilton, co-located with FM&#39;06), FORMED (Budapest, at ETAPS 2008), and FMET 2008 (Kitakyushu 2008, co-located with ICFEM). The latest event was TFM2009, the 2nd International FME Conference on Teaching Formal Methods, in November 2009 in Eindhoven, the Netherlands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submission Information</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/home/submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/home/submission/</guid>
      <description>FMTea19 invites high quality papers reporting on opinions, approaches, experiences, and empirical studies related to the topic of teaching Formal Methods. Each submitted paper will be reviewed by at least three PC members. The proceedings will be published as an LNCS volume, either as part of the FM Satellite Events LNCS proceedings or as a separate LNCS volume. (The exact nature of the proceedings will depend on the number of accepted papers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>